http://www.fishers-boise.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement | Fisher's Technology | Office Supplies
Skip to content
COVID-19 Updates
Welcome!
Privacy Statement
Fisher's Technology is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Fisher's Technology Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Fisher's Technology website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Fisher's Technology collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Fisher's Technology also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Fisher's Technology. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Fisher's Technology for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fisher's Technology Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Fisher's Technology public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Fisher's Technology does not read any of your private online communications.
Fisher's Technology encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Fisher's Technology so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Fisher's Technology is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Fisher's Technology and Fisher's Technology family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Fisher's Technology collects and uses your personal information to operate the Fisher's Technology Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Fisher's Technology also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fisher's Technology and its affiliates. Fisher's Technology may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Fisher's Technology does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Fisher's Technology may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Fisher's Technology may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fisher's Technology, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Fisher's Technology does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Fisher's Technology keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Fisher's Technology, in order to determine what Fisher's Technology services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fisher's Technology to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Fisher's Technology Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fisher's Technology or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fisher's Technology; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fisher's Technology, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Fisher's Technology Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Fisher's Technology's pages, or register with Fisher's Technology site or services, a cookie helps Fisher's Technology to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Fisher's Technology Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Fisher's Technology features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fisher's Technology services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Fisher's Technology secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Fisher's Technology secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Fisher's Technology will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fisher's Technology encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fisher's Technology is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Fisher's Technology welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fisher's Technology has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fisher's Technology at info@fisherstech.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Fisher’s manages IT environments, sells and services copiers and printers, and streamlines business operations with document management and related software solutions. Fisher’s mission is to make customers extremely happy while having a great time.
Copiers / Printers
Copiers / MultifunctionLaser PrinterFax SolutionsWide Format / PlottersProduction PrintScanners3D PrintersLive Local Support
IT Services
NetworkingSecurityBackup and Business ContinuityCloud HostingDevice ManagementProductivity SolutionsIT Help Desk and SupportProfessional ServicesCompliancy ServicesUnified Communications
Document Management
Solution ServicesDocument ManagementElectronic FormsImaging / OCRIntegration / Routing / WorkflowFax SolutionsCost RecoveryUser Accounting
Copyright © 2018 Fisher's Technology. All Rights Reserved. Developed by REDFOX VISUAL.
ACCOUNT LOGIN | PRIVACY STATEMENT | TERMS OF USE
×
Scroll To Top
Please share your location to continue
